(upbeat R&B music)
♪ This is what you do ♪
♪ You make me wanna
leave the one I'm with ♪
♪ Start a new relationship with you ♪
♪ This is what you do ♪
♪ Think about a ring and all the
things that come along with ♪
♪ You make me ♪
♪ You make me wanna
leave the one I'm with ♪
♪ Start a new relationship with you ♪
♪ This is what you do ♪
♪ Think about a ring and all the
things that come along with ♪
♪ You make me ♪
♪ Before anything began between us ♪
♪ You were like my best friend ♪
♪ The one I used to run and talk to ♪
♪ When me and my girl
was having problems ♪
♪ That's right ♪
♪ You used to say it'll be okay ♪
♪ Suggest little nice things I should do ♪
♪ And when I go home at
night and lay my head down ♪
♪ All I seem to think about was you ♪
♪ And how you make me wanna
leave the one I'm with ♪
♪ Start a new relationship with you ♪
♪ This is what you do ♪
♪ Think about a ring and all the
things that come along with ♪
♪ You make me ♪
♪ You make me wanna
leave the one I'm with ♪
♪ Start a new relationship with you ♪
♪ This is what you do ♪
♪ Think about a ring and all the
things that come along with ♪
♪ You make me ♪
♪ Now what's bad is you're
the one that hooked us up ♪
♪ Knowing it should have been you ♪
♪ What's sad is that I love
her but I'm falling for you ♪
♪ What should I do ♪
♪ Should I tell my baby bye-bye ♪
♪ Should I do exactly what I feel inside ♪
♪ 'Cause, I, I don't wanna
go, don't need to stay ♪
♪ But I really need to get it together ♪
♪ You make me wanna
leave the one I'm with ♪
♪ Start a new relationship with you ♪
♪ This is what you do ♪
♪ Say what you do ♪
♪ Think about a ring and all the
things that come along with ♪
♪ You make me ♪
♪ You make me wanna
leave the one I'm with ♪
♪ Start a new relationship with you ♪
♪ This is what you do ♪
♪ Think about a ring and all the
things that come along with ♪
♪ You make me ♪
♪ At this point the
situation's outta control ♪
♪ I never meant to hurt her ♪
♪ But I gotta let her
go, gotta let her go ♪
♪ And she may not understand it ♪
♪ While all of this is going on ♪
♪ I tried, I tried to fight it ♪
♪ But the feeling's just too strong ♪
♪ You make, make, make me ♪
♪ You make me wanna ♪
♪ Oh, you make, make, me, me ♪
♪ Oh babe ♪
♪ You make me wanna ♪
♪ Do your thing ♪
♪ Come along wit' it ♪
♪ You makin' me ♪
♪ You make me wanna
leave the one I'm with ♪
♪ Start a new relationship with you ♪
♪ This is what you do ♪
♪ Think about a ring and all the
things that come along with ♪
♪ You make me ♪
♪ You make me wanna
leave the one I'm with ♪
♪ Start a new relationship with you ♪